http://www.josephpatrickmoore.com/privacy-policy.html

>
Path To Geshe (Soundtrack)
privacy policy
Effective: January 1, 1996Last Updated: June 2017JOSEPHPATRICKMOORE.COM PRIVACY POLICY - We Never Share Your InformationJoseph Patrick Moore and this site care about your privacy.  This privacy policy tells you what information we collect at our web site(s) and how we use it. If you choose to visit any of the Blue Canoe Digital web sites, your visit is subject to this privacy policy, and you agree to the terms of it.WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECTThere are several places at our sites where you can share your personal information with us, and where you can communicate with others.Newsletters and Other Communications from Us. Our users and customers may receive newsletters, email communications, or communications through other channels for, among other purposes, the promotion and marketing of a product or service from JPM, our artist's and record label division, and we may also offer visitors to our sites the opportunity to sign up to receive such information. When there is a separate sign-up for newsletters, we ask for contact information such as name and email address, and, sometimes, demographic and profile information. By visiting our sites, you affirmatively consent to our collection and use of your data. We use this information in the same manner as we use the contact information in the Registration process described above. Recipients of our mailings can unsubscribe by following instructions that may appear at the end of email communications. Note that in order to keep our registered users informed about the operation of our services, we may send emails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our sites and service.Communications with Us. We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contacting us with a question or feedback). We may retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.Contests, Sweepstakes and Surveys. We may also have contests, sweepstakes and surveys at our sites. When you enter or participate in them, we request contact information from you (such as your full name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number) and may also request demographic or profile information. We will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (for example, to contact you if you have won). We may also use the information to send you newsletters and other information we think may be of interest. Recipients of our mailings can unsubscribe by following instructions that may appear at the end of the email communication. Any personal information we collect may be associated with registration information.  We may sometimes partner with sponsors in offering contests, sweepstakes or surveys, and may share (provide and receive) information with them. By entering or participating in such contests, sweepstakes, and surveys, you affirmatively consent to our collection and use of your data.AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTIONWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web sites.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites and other web sites on the Internet in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like to learn more about this practice or find out how you can opt out from allowing these companies to gather this information or use it to display targeted ads, please visit the NAI’s website at http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp. Most common web browsers today, such as Safari, Firefox and Internet Explorer, allow you to modify your settings to block cookies entirely, alert you every time they are being sent, or allow their use by only those web sites you choose.  You can also delete cookies that are currently stored on your computer’s hard drive.  To do this within Firefox or Internet Explorer, go to Tools, then Options or Internet Options, and then choose the Privacy tab to make your selections.  If you choose to disable cookies, certain features on our web sites may not be available or work properly.  Also, please note that if you disable/delete all cookies stored on your computer, you will have also disabled the cookies that are used by NAI to help prevent you from receiving unwanted advertising from third party ad networks.  If you do not want this to happen, please make sure not to disable/delete the NAI cookie or add NAI to the approved list of sites from whom you allow/accept cookies.WITH WHOM YOUR INFORMATION IS SHAREDWe never share your information, period.CHOICEBy accepting this privacy policy, you expressly choose to receive certain communications from us, and you expressly agree to the privacy practices described herein. Our sites may also provide you with additional specific opportunities to select communications you wish to receive. You may change your privacy preferences, e.g. choose to cease receiving certain communications, by informing us of your new preferences. We will be able to honor your new preferences most quickly if you inform us of them by following the appropriate instructions in any communication you receive from us. To change your privacy preferences with respect to those communications, please go to the profile page at the site where you provided your personal information or direct your instructions to the Contact identified at the end of this policy. ACCESSIf a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), we endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user's personal data. Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions regarding making changes to your data.DATA COLLECTION FROM CHILDRENWe strive to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect personal information from U.S. children under 13 without appropriate parental notice and consent. Sites that are directed to children where personal information is collected should have a Children's Privacy Policy setting forth our COPPA-compliant practices. We actively screen-out children from data collection and/or use of interactive or community features. We are committed to protecting children's privacy.NOTICE: Visit www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children's privacy online.SECURITYSecurity for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. We store your personal information securely, and use special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.MERCHANT/E-COMMERCE AREASWe generally make e-commerce offerings at our sites. Some of our sites do have merchant/e-commerce areas, where users can purchase merchandise. Personal information collected at those areas is not shared without the purchasers' consent. At each of those areas, we endeavor to provide a privacy policy link where users can review the privacy policies that apply to data collection and use at those areas, and we urge our users to review them.LINKSWe may provide links to non-JosephPatrickMoore.com sites. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users, and we advise you to check their privacy policies.PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESWe reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this policy from time to time. Changes to this privacy policy are effective at the time they are posted and your continued use of our sites after posting will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.CONTACTIf you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:JosephPatrickMoore.comc/o Blue Canoe DIgital, LLCPO Box 777143Henderson, NV 89077
All contents © 1996-2020  JPM, Blue Canoe Records & Blue Canoe Digital LLC All Rights Reserved.
Path To Geshe (Soundtrack)
